{
    "subject": "resource/Lujo_Brentano",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_G\u00f6ttingen",
    "human_readable": "Lujo Brentano attended University of G\u00f6ttingen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9875895380973816,
            "question": "Was Lujo Brentano a student at the University of G\u00f6ttingen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.986312210559845,
            "question": "Did Lujo Brentano pursue his studies at the University of G\u00f6ttingen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9791551232337952,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Lujo Brentano and the University of G\u00f6ttingen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9547663927078247,
            "question": "Where did Lujo Brentano attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9448431730270386,
            "question": "What is the name of the university that Lujo Brentano attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8762917518615723,
            "question": "What university was Lujo Brentano associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.802215576171875,
            "question": "To what university did Lujo Brentano go for his studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852668166160583,
            "question": "In what institution did Lujo Brentano study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783277153968811,
            "question": "Which university played a role in Lujo Brentano's academic journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6581899523735046,
            "question": "What is known about Lujo Brentano's education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lujo Brentano attended University of G\u00f6ttingen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5806_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which university played a role in Lujo Brentano's academic journey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5806_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what institution did Lujo Brentano study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5806_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To what university did Lujo Brentano go for his studies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5806_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5806_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5806/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt mentions that Lujo Brentano studied in Dublin (Trinity College), M\u00fcnster, Munich, Heidelberg (doctorate in law), W\u00fcrzburg, and G\u00f6ttingen (doctorate in economics). It is implied that he attended the University of G\u00f6ttingen for his doctorate in economics."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Lujo Brentano studied at the University of G\u00f6ttingen, which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}